NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
Friend!
What did you say?!
You mean to say that only rookies
went after Sasuke?!
It really couldn't be helped...
the situation in
the Village being how it is...
And anyway...
I've taken the minimally
required measures.
Hey, hey!
Your mission has already
been assigned!
Uh, I'm gonna go do an errand
and will be back shortly...
Don't worry.
Jeez...
Kakashi-sensei!
It's already been two days
since Sasuke-kun left the village...
And Naruto and the others who went in
pursuit haven't come back either.
And neither has Lee-san...
I know. I've more or less
heard the whole story.
I... believe in Naruto!
I believe him, but if something were
to happen to Naruto and Sasuke-kun...
Sakura, you don't need to
worry about anything.
Leave this to me.
Summoning Jutsu!
First of all, I want you guys to
fan out in all directions
in pursuit of Naruto
and Sasuke's scent.
Naruto and Sasuke you said?
Did something happen
to the two of them?
I'll explain later...
Right now, time is of essence.
Okay.
As soon as you confirm that
you've detected the scent,
call me and I'll be there immediately.
All right! Scatter!
Well, I guess since she saw them
fight before her very eyes...
it's useless to tell her
not to worry.
Stop!
Damn...
I can't stop...
Sasuke... Stop with revenge.
What?!
Even if you were successful
in carrying out your revenge,
all that will come out of it
is a sense of emptiness.
Shut up!
What do you know?!
Don't say that so knowingly!
Well... calm down.
Neither you nor I could
call ourselves lucky.
Of that much I'm certain.
But it could be worse.
Both you and I have found
precious comrades, right?
We understand that all the more
because we've lost them once.
I taught you Chidori
because you now have
precious people.
That power isn't something to be used
against your comrades or for revenge.
You know what that power
should be used for.
I'm gonna win no matter what!
Don't get so carried away!
I was too naive...
Watching them, they might actually
be intent on killing each other...
Kakashi-sensei...
Please let me get there
in time!
I already said this earlier but...
In truth, you were waiting
for this too, weren't you?
Neither Kakashi nor Sakura
are present right now.
So there's nobody here to stop us
like that time before.
You...!
This time around we're gonna
settle this for real!
I will take you down!
Chidori!
You idiot...
Same here!
I'm gonna beat you senseless...
and take you back home even
if I have to drag you!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Rasengan!
It wasn't meaningless...
To me, you became
my closest friend.
Sasuke actually came out
and said that... to me...
And that's exactly the reason why
I wanted to verify it using this Rasengan.
Damn...
Damn you!
He was able to counter
my full power of Chidori
to that extent...
That jutsu...
Damn...
Naruto, to what extent...!
That failure...
Naruto...!
Well, your limit is two blows...
that's about it.
And if I try to use more than that...
what will happen?
The third blow won't initiate.
Remember that well.
If you try to initiate
the Jutsu forcibly...
not only will the Art not
initiate properly,
but your Chakra will become zero...
In the worst case scenario
it will cost you your life!
Damn... I can't waste a blow...
It wouldn't serve any purpose
if we cancel each other like earlier.
There's... no longer
any mistake about this.
You... really intended...
You really intended to...
Sasuke...!
I will use numerous speedy techniques
and Jutsu to create an opening.
And then... I will make
a hit with Chidori.
Sasuke...
Did you know, Naruto...
Top-class Ninja should be
able to read each other's hearts
simply by an exchange of fists.
Even without saying anything...
You're naive, Naruto.
How about it?
Were you really able
to read inside...
this heart of mine?
Fire Style:
Phoenix Flower Jutsu!
Sasuke... I knew that you
were always alone.
At first, I was relieved
when I found out
that there was
a guy similar to myself.
And it also made me happy...
To tell the truth, I really wanted
to approach you right away.
But... I wasn't able to approach you...
— Awesome...
— You're incredible...
You were always able
to do everything.
And moreover, you were always
being praised by everyone.
Because you and I
were so different...
Because I didn't want to admit it,
I decided to call you my rival.
I didn't want to lose to you...
and I felt that even more strongly...
because I was called a failure.
Even when we were in Team 7,
I continued to feel
the same way the whole time.
I'm stubborn...
And wasn't able to express
what I really felt...
What I really wanted was
to become like you.
You were what I aspired to... so...
You are one of the ones I want to fight.
I was really happy when
you said that!
Those were your first words...
acknowledging me...
You and I both knew,
without us even having to
have an exchange of fists!
From that time on...
Even without saying anything...
The fact that...
we are friends!
It's not without meaning...
To me you're...
my closest friend.
However... you're trying to
take me down for real.
Right now, I don't really know
whether you really meant
what you said earlier or not.
Thinking that we were friends...
That might have been...
That might have been just me...
It's too late now!
Naruto!
If that's the case... I'm...
really lame, aren't I...
Sasuke!
But...
It can't be helped, can it?
I don't know why but...
I don't know why...
But I...
I...
don't want you...
you to be taken away
by someone like Orochimaru!
You managed to divert it
with your left hand,
but it was meaningless.
You won't be able to use
any hand sign
or that Jutsu earlier anymore.
This is the end!
Wh-What's...
that red Chakra...?
Where does he get that
kind of power from?!
W-What the hell... is this?!
His shoulder injury is healing...
That's unbelievable!
Sasuke! I'm not gonna let
Orochimaru take you away!
I will stop you,
even if I have to break every bone
in your arms and legs!
hitotsu hitotsu omoidaseba
when I recalled the parts one by one,
subete wakatteita kigashite ita no ni
I felt as though I had understood everything
iroaseta kotoba wa
faded words
boku no sugu soba ni oite atta
which I kept so close to me
kotae no denai yoru to
speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
hitokira no nukumori to
and this distant yearning for you
haruka kanata no akogare to
I live,
tada sore dake wo
simply repeating this cycle
kurikaeshi boku wa ikite iru
held in my two hands
kono ryoute ni kakaete iru mono
a droplet of time
toki no shizuku
softly clutching forgotten memories
sotto nigirishimete wasureta kioku
lost words
nakushita kotoba
I'll keep these thoughts...
kono omoi wa
Don't you talk stupid like that!
I don't care what
you're thinking anymore!
I won't let you go to Orochimaru's
place no matter what!
I'm taking you back to the village
even if I have to drag you there!
Sasuke! You're my...
Next time:
"Tearfull Yell! You Are My Friend."